Get back! Get back!
回去！回去！
Please! Wait! I've got to talk to you!
拜托，等等！我要跟你们谈谈！
Keep away!
走开！
Exterminate!
终结！
_ or you'll be caught in the time field!
We warned you.
我们警告过你
Yes, yes, so you did.
是的，是的，是这样
This may come as a shock to you, but you've just
travelled two hundred years through time.
有一点可能会让你感到震惊, 但你刚刚穿越了两百年的时间
Thank you. But I'm probably more familiar
with the concept of time travel than you are.
谢谢。但我可能比你更熟悉时间旅行的概念
Now wait a minute.
Before the time transference, I saw a Dalek.
现在等一下，在时间转移之前, 我看到了一个 Dalek
- You know of the Daleks?  - Indeed I do.
- 你知道 Dalek ？ - 我确实知道
I know them only too well.
They've been my bitterest enemy for many years.
我太了解他们了。他们多年来一直是我最痛苦的敌人
Then you're a fool to have
let yourself be brought here!
那你让自己被带到这里来，就太傻了
Look, I came here in order to find Miss Jo Grant.
听着，我来这里是为了找到 Jo Geant 小姐
I told you, she's probably dead.
我告诉过你, 她可能已经死了
But as long as there's a chance...
但只要还有一线可能...
Come on, Anat.
快点，Anat
Wait a minute - what is my best way of finding her?
等一下 - 我找到她的最好方法是什么？
That's your problem.
那是你的问题
We can't just leave him!
我们不能抛下他！
I can - come!
我能 - 走！
Run, Doctor - run!
跑，博士 - 快跑！
Report!
汇报！
The security guards have combed the tunnels.
They've found nothing.
保安已经对隧道进行了排查。他们什么也没发现
You have failed the Daleks!
You will be punished!
你辜负了 Dalek! 你将会受到惩罚!
The fault is not mine!
Your security guards let them get away.
错不是我的! 你们的警卫让他们跑了
- Those creatures are useless!
- They are loyal to the Daleks.
- 那些生物一点用没有!  - 他们对 Dalek 很忠诚
As loyal as they are stupid!
They will never be a match for human guerillas.
同样也很愚蠢! 他们永远不会是人类游击队的对手
No one can succeed who opposes the Daleks.
跟 Dalek 作对的人没一个成功
For every guerilla cell that you destroy,
another one springs up.
你每消灭一个游击队成员, 另一个又站起来了
They have stolen your time machines
and copied them.
他们偷了你们的时间机器, 还复制了它们
They steal your weapons, your explosives.
他们偷了你们的武器，你们的炸药
These criminals will be exterminated.
The Daleks will destroy them.
这些罪犯将会被终结。Dalek 将摧毁他们
If only you would let me recruit
more human security guards...
要是你们能让我招募更多的人类保安就好了...
Humans are treacherous and unreliable!
人类都很狡猾，不可靠!
Not all humans. I have served you faithfully.
并非所有人这样，我就一直忠实地为你们服务
Do not dispute with the Daleks!
Obey without question!
不要与 Dalek 争辩! 毫无疑问地服从!
Very well. There was one... curious thing.
好吧。有一件...奇特的事情
The girl referred to a companion in her own time zone.
那个女孩提到她那个时区的一个同伴
She called him... "the Doctor".
她称呼他为...“博士”
Doctor?! Did you say "Doctor"?!
博士?! 你刚才是说了“博士”吗？
He appears to have got through to our time.
He was seen by the guards.
他似乎也穿越到我们这个时代了, 警卫看见他了
The Doctor is an enemy of the Daleks!
He must be found at once and exterminated!
博士是 Dalek 的敌人！必须立刻找到他, 予以终结！
Don't gloss over it, Anat, we failed!
别掩饰了, Anat, 我们失败了！
We had no choice once our plan was known to them.
一旦我们的计划被他们所知晓, 我们就没有选择了
If you'd listened to me,
we still could have done what was needed.
如果你当初听我的, 我们可能已经完成所需要做的了
We did all we could!
我们已经尽了我们所能！
Monia, our orders were to eliminate Styles, right?
Monia, 我们的命令是消灭 Styles, 对吧？
Yes, but you failed.
是的, 但你失败了
We could have succeeded.
我们本来可以胜利的
Then why didn't you?
那为什么你们没有？
He wasn't there! Security guards found us.
他不在那里！保安队又找到了我们
But Anat went soft.
但是 Anat 心软了
Be quiet.
闭嘴
The trouble with you, Boaz is...
你的问题，Boaz，是...
Both of you! We have to think now.
The situation is different.
你俩都闭嘴！我们必须得想想了，处境不同了
As I see it, it's exactly the same -
we still have a job to do.
就我所见，完全一样，我们还是有活要干
No. There may be other ways.
I've had a report from one of our contacts.
不，可能有其它的路子。我收到一个线人的报告
A girl has been captured.
They're holding her prisoner at the control centre.
他们抓住了一个女孩儿，正把她扣押在控制中心
The same girl - the one who operated
the time module at Styles' house?
就那个女孩儿吗？就在 Styles 房子里打开了时间模块的那个？
It fits your description.
跟你的描述相符
Well, at least she's alive.
哦，至少她还活着
In the hands of the Daleks? She won't live long.
在 Dalek 的手上？她活不长了
Can she tell them anything?
她会给他们透露什么吗？
Nothing of importance.
Have they picked up that Doctor yet?
没什么重要的。他们已经找到了博士没有？
Not yet. It's only a matter of time.
还没有，不过只是时间的问题
Move! Move! Come along there, you scum!
走！快走！到那边去，你们这些渣子
Move! Come along there, move! Move! Go on!
走！到那边去，走！继续！
Well?
怎样？
Been captured. Taken for processing.
We must rescue him.
被抓住了，被带去处理。我们必须救他
Rescue him? Are you mad?! From there?
救他？你疯了？到那儿去救？
I say we must!
我说了必须！
Suicide.
自杀
Are you afraid?
你害怕了？
Me? Of course I am. I'm not a fool.
What is he to us?
我？当然害怕，我又不是傻子。他是我们什么人？
We have fresh information from
one of our contacts at control centre.
我们从控制中心的线人那里收到了新消息
He is the sworn enemy of the Daleks.
He is the one man they're afraid of - don't you see?
他是 Dalek 的宿敌，是他们所害怕的一个人，你明白了吗？
It's our only hope. If we don't act quickly,
it may be too late.
这是我们仅有的希望。不过我们不赶紧行动, 恐怕就来不及了
You are the Doctor! You are an enemy of the Daleks!
你是博士！你是 Dalek 的敌人！
Now you are in our power! You will be exterminated!
现在你在我们手上了！你将被终结！
You will be exterminated! You will be exterminated!
你将被终结！你将被终结！你将被终结！你将被终结！